<resources>
    <string name="terms_of_service_text_pwcs"></string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_text">
    <![CDATA[
                <center><b>CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup></b></center><br/><br/><center><b>(scroll down)</b></center><br/><br/><br/>Before using the App, please carefully read this agreement relating to your use of the App.  By using the App, User Agrees to be bound by these Terms and Conditions and by Tech 4 Good&apos;s privacy policy (collectively herein as &ldquo;Terms and Conditions&rdquo;). If User does not agree to these Terms and Conditions, do not use Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> App.<br/><br/>These Terms of Use and Conditions are a legal agreement (&ldquo;Agreement&rdquo;) between Tech 4 Good LLC (also as &ldquo;We&rdquo;, &ldquo;Us&rdquo; and &ldquo;Our&rdquo;) and you, the &ldquo;User&rdquo; (also as &ldquo;I&rdquo; and &ldquo;Your&rdquo;) of the application and governs access and use of the Circle of 6® App and/or Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> App (&ldquo;App&rdquo;).  For purposes of these Terms of Use, the words &ldquo;User&rdquo;, &ldquo;your&rdquo;, &ldquo;I&rdquo; or other like terms shall refer to the party agreeing to these Terms of Use and to any person or entity who, uses the App (collectively herein as &ldquo;User&rdquo;).  Collectively Tech 4 Good and User are the &ldquo;Parties&rdquo;.<br/><br/>READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY. THIS AGREEMENT CONTAINS IMPORTANT TERMS GOVERNING THE SERVICES PROVIDED BY TECH 4 GOOD REGARIDNG CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup>, YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES AND TECH 4 GOOD&apos;S OBLIGATIONS, AND INCLUDES LIMITS ON TECH 4 GOOD&apos;S LIABILITY, INDEMNITY AND OTHER IMPORTANT CLAUSES.<br/><br/>Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> is a mobile application that encourages the social networking of its users by connecting them with others to assist them in various situations. When User uses Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> on a communications network, cellular network, or other network or system having charges for data transfer and/or communications, the provider&apos;s rates will apply as charges to User.<br/><br/>The Services provided by the Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> consist solely of providing social networking of persons, entities or agencies.<br/><br/>Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> software and/or application should not be relied upon for emergency services and is in no way designed to serve as an alternative to the emergency services provided by 911 telephone service.  If User has an emergency, or important time-sensitive crime information, medical information or other important information communicate this information with by 911 emergency telephone service.<br/><br/>18+ Years of Age Required to use the App:  Tech 4 Good requires all users to be at least 18 years of age to purchase any merchandise or to sign up for any service. By downloading and activating the App User is confirming that User is of adult age.  Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> is intended for users 18 years or over.<br/><br/><b>Parties Are Independent</b><br/><br/>User Agrees that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship exists between User and Tech 4 Good as a result of these Terms of Use or your use of the App. Tech 4 Good &apos;s performance of these Terms of Use is subject to existing laws and legal process, and nothing contained in these Terms of Use is in derogation of Tech 4 Good &apos;s right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requests or requirements relating to your use of the App or information provided to or gathered by Tech 4 Good with respect to such use.<br/><br/>The information provided on the Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> site is free of charge and for informational purposes only and does not create a business or professional services relationship between User and Tech 4 Good.<br/><br/><b>Entire Agreement</b><br/><br/>Unless otherwise specified herein, these Terms of Use constitutes the entire agreement between User and Tech 4 Good (the &ldquo;Parties&rdquo;, each respectively a &ldquo;Party&rdquo;) with respect to the App and it supersedes any prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral or written, between the user and Tech 4 Good with respect to the App.  User confirms that User has not entered into this Contract on the basis of any representation that is not expressly incorporated into this Contract.  I am not relying on Tech 4 Good and/or Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup>&apos;s advice or advertisements. Tech 4 Good is not bound by any representation, promise, condition, inducement or warranty, express or implied, that is not included in writing in this contract.<br/><br/>By acceptance of these Terms and Conditions, user has accepted a legally enforceable online contract, and additionally has agreed upon the terms and conditions set forth in these &ldquo;Terms and Conditions&rdquo; governing your transaction with Tech 4 Good and use of the App.<br/><br/>Should there arise any conflict between this Agreement and User&apos;s download request, purchase order or other document, these &ldquo;Terms and Conditions&rdquo; will govern, whether any such document is prior to or subsequent to this Agreement.<br/><br/>The provisions in this Agreement are for the sole benefit of User and Tech 4 Good and the assigns of Tech 4 Good and shall not inure to the benefit of any other person either as a third party beneficiary or otherwise.<br/><br/><b>User Responsibilities</b>By Using the App, User Agrees that: (i) your App account and device password are personal to User and may not be used by anyone else to access the App or any Tech 4 Good Site; (ii) User will not do anything which would assist anyone who is not a registered user to gain access to the App; and (iii) User will not create registration accounts for the purpose of abusing the functionality of the App; nor will User seek to pass yourself off as another user.  User Agrees to discontinue use of the App if User becomes aware any unauthorized use of your device password or account identifiers by others.  Tech 4 Good cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from a user&apos;s failure keep device passwords confidential including any loss or damage arising from any Users failure to protect and secure User&apos;s communication device and/or phone.<br/><br/>Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> services requires the installation and/or activation of an App and/or application and/or app and a compatible computer, cell phone or PDA with Internet, telephone communications, text and e-mail access.<br/><br/>The Parties hereto agree that the App, once downloaded, is in the exclusive possession and control of the User, and it is User&apos;s sole responsibility to test the operation of the App and confirm it is operational. The App will not function without proper phone, communications and/or network services.  The user is solely responsible for having compatible and active phone and/or communications services.  The App will also not function without sufficient battery power for a communications device or without an active signal.  The user is solely responsible for having a functioning device and sufficient communications signal and service.  User is obligated to pay your telephone, electricity and other bills timely and to ensure that your telephone and electricity is such that the App is not affected.  In the event that User has a prepaid telephone and no radio transmitter, User hereby acknowledges that in order for the App to function your telephone must be sufficiently functioning.<br/><br/>User is obliged to maintain and update contact information for the App with whom the App may communicate when so activated by User.  User Agrees to: (1) provide true, accurate, current, and complete information about yourself and/or your organization, as appropriate, as prompted by the Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> registration form or any other form, including, but not limited to, your e-mail address for notices and any other communications; (2) maintain and promptly update the foregoing to keep it true, accurate, current, and complete; and (3) provide any other information that Tech 4 Good may request of User from time to time for purposes reasonably related to your use of the App.  It is Your responsibility to keep Your Personal Information up to date at all times.<br/><br/>User Agrees to use reasonable efforts to take precautions against the contamination of your computer systems and files by software viruses, worms or other malicious agents. At a minimum, such precautions shall include the installation, upgrading and use of commercial virus detection software to scan communications, files, data and documents transmitted to and/or by User using the App.<br/><br/>In the event the User utilizes the App, the User shall be obligated for and agrees to pay any costs and expenses incurred including, but not limited to, response, police, fire, ambulance, physician or other medical assistance in obtaining assistance, or cost whatsoever incurred as a result of the User&apos;s use of the App.  User shall be responsible for any taxes which Tech 4 Good may be required to pay or collect under any applicable law in connection with the Services.  System remains property of Tech 4 Good.  Fees may be required for some services.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good has the sole discretion to determine the fees charged to User for using its web site or Services. Fees for Tech 4 Good services may vary by jurisdiction or geography. Tech 4 Good reserves the right to change its fee structure at any time.  It is your responsibility to verify costs in advance of ordering services.  By accepting or using the Tech 4 Good web site or Services after such notice of changes has been posted on its web site, User Agrees to be bound by any such fee changes.<br/><br/><b>Limitations On User&apos;s Use Of The App</b><br/><br/>By using the Circle of 6® web site and/or any Tech 4 Good website and/or the App, User represents, affirms and declares that: (1) all business User conduct through Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> is lawful and that User is subject to civil and criminal penalties should User violate those laws and regulations which may apply to such business; and (2) User acknowledge that any information provided by Tech 4 Good to User in the course of performing the Services may be derived from private or government agency databases with respect to which Tech 4 Good has no control, and that Tech 4 Good shall have no liability whatsoever with respect to such information, including, without limitation, in the event any such information is inaccurate, out of date, contains errors or omissions, or is otherwise incorrect in any way.<br/><br/>As a condition of your use of the App, User warrants to Tech 4 Good that User will not use the App for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms of Use. User may not use the App in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the App or interfere with any other party&apos;s use and enjoyment of the App.  User Agrees to use the App only to communicate, post, send and receive messages and material that are proper and related to the App.  User shall not engage in any illegal or abusive behavior by use of the App.  User shall not locate another user through the App if applicable laws do not permit such action.  Use the App or the Communication Services for any purpose other than as consistent with the purpose of the App is prohibited.  User has no right to sublicense or sell the App to any party.  User may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the App and/or application or services.  User may not modify, adapt or hack the App or modify another software and/or application so as to falsely imply that it is associated with Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup>.  User may not claim a telephone number for use in your Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> account which does not belong to User.  User will not engage in spamming or harassing communications.<br/><br/>User may not use Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> services for any purpose other than social networking. Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> services or related materials may not be sold, rented or otherwise commercialized with third parties.<br/><br/>User Agrees not to sell, resell, or offer for any commercial purposes, any portion of the App, or access to the App.  Any use of any of the materials on this site other than for private, personal, non-commercial viewing purposes is strictly prohibited.<br/><br/>Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> reserves the right to investigate and prosecute violations of any of the above to the fullest extent of the law. Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request.<br/><br/>User agrees not to reverse engineer, disassemble, decompile, convert into human-readable format, or otherwise attempt to derive the source code of any software included in or related to the App.  User agrees not to copy any ideas, features, functions or graphics of or related to the App.  Tech 4 Good may involve and cooperate with law enforcement authorities in prosecuting users who violate these Terms of Use. Tech 4 Good has no obligation to monitor the Communication Services. However, Tech 4 Good reserves the right to review the use of and/or materials posted to a Communication Service and to remove any materials in its sole discretion at any time.<br/><br/>User is prohibited from posting or transmitting any advertising &ldquo;spam,&rdquo; unlawful material, or other material we deem otherwise inappropriate for our site. TECH 4 GOOD DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY ARISING FROM, CONNECTED TO, OR ASSOCIATED WITH THE CONTENT OF ANY USER POSTINGS. User Agrees to refrain from undertaking any activity that imposes an unreasonable or disproportionate burden on our site. Tech 4 Good reserves the sole discretion to deny, revoke, or otherwise restrict the access privileges of any user who at any time fails to comply with these Terms and Conditions.<br/><br/><b>Assignment and transfer</b><br/><br/>Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> is entitled to transfer all of its rights and obligations under this Agreement to another party without your consent and User hereby accepts and approves any such transfer of Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup>&apos;s rights and obligations. In the event of such transfer, Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup>&apos;s rights and obligations to User under this Agreement shall automatically be discharged. We are at all times entitled to engage contractors or sub-contractors to carry out all or any of our obligations under this Agreement.  This Agreement is not assignable by User. This Agreement or any portion thereof is assignable by Tech 4 Good in its sole discretion.  User is not entitled to cede, delegate or otherwise transfer your rights and obligations under this Agreement to any other party.<br/><br/><b>Privacy Policy</b><br/><br/>Tech 4 Good is committed to protecting Your privacy. This Privacy Policy and Our Terms and Conditions explain how We will deal with any Personal Information that We collect or that is provided to Us about User.<br/><br/>By entering into this Contract, User gives Your consent to the Personal Information being used and released in accordance with these Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy.  Tech 4 Good maintains an online privacy policy at http://www.circleof6app.com/privacy-policy that is applicable to the terms, conditions and obligations of the parties to this Contract.  Tech 4 Good handles user Registration Data in accordance with Tech 4 Good&apos;s Privacy Policy.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, in Tech 4 Good&apos;s sole discretion.<br/><br/>We may use aggregated and anonymized Personal Information and statistics for the purposes of analyzing use of Our software and/or application and Service and may provide such aggregated and anonymized Personal Information to third parties. These statistics will not include Personal Information that can be used to identify any individual.<br/><br/>User agrees that we can use the User&apos;s communications device and other information to let User know about other activities including goods and services offered by Tech 4 Good or third parties which We think may be of interest to User.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good can change our Privacy Policy at any time for any reason.  Continued use of Our Service and/or purchase of Our Goods will indicate that User Agrees to any such changes. We will use Personal Information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.  It is User&apos;s responsibility to monitor an review the privacy policy frequently.<br/><br/><b>Links</b><br/><br/>Links on the Circle of 6 site may lead to services or App not operated by Tech 4 Good.  Tech 4 Good exercises no control whatsoever over such other software and/or applications and web-based resources and is not responsible or liable for the availability thereof or the Content, advertising, products or other materials thereon.  No judgment or warranty is made with respect to such other services or App and Tech 4 Good takes no responsibility for such other App or services. A link to another site or service is not an endorsement of that site or service. Any use User make of the information provided on this site, or any site or service linked to by this site, is at your own risk.  Tech 4 Good shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss incurred or suffered by any user in connection therewith. Your access and use of linked software and/or applications, including information, material, products and services therein, is solely at your own risk.<br/><br/><b>User Responsibility</b><br/><br/>All information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, video, messages, or any other materials whatsoever (collectively, \"Content\"), whether publicly posted or privately transmitted, is the sole responsibility of the User from whom such Content originated. This means that the User, and not Tech 4 Good, is entirely responsible for all Content that he or she uploads, posts, emails, communicates or otherwise transmits via the App. No user shall transmit Content or otherwise conduct or participate in any activities on the App, software and/or application that, in the judgment of Tech 4 Good, is likely to be prohibited by law in any applicable jurisdiction, including laws governing the encryption of software, the export of technology, the transmission of obscenity, or the permissible uses of intellectual property.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good reserves the right to refuse or delete any Content of which it becomes aware and reasonably deems not to fulfill the purpose of the App.  Tech 4 Good does not control the Content communicated by User and, as such, does not guarantee the accuracy, integrity or quality of such Content. Under no circumstances will Tech 4 Good be liable in any way for any Content, including, but not limited to, liability for any errors or omissions in any Content or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any Content posted, emailed or otherwise transmitted via the App.<br/><br/><b>Intellectual Property</b><br/><br/>Unless otherwise noted, all text, images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, video clips, and other materials that are part of our site (collectively the &ldquo;Materials&rdquo;) are copyrighted works, trademarks, trade dress, or other intellectual properties owned, controlled, or licensed by Tech 4 Good or used under principles of &ldquo;fair use.&rdquo; The Materials and the site as a whole are intended solely for your personal use. User may download or copy the Materials for such personal use, provided that User does not remove any copyright or other proprietary notices contained on the Materials. By allowing User to download these Materials for personal use, we expressly do not transfer to User any right, title, or interest in the Materials.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good respects the intellectual property rights of others, and requires that the people who use the Tech 4 Good site(s), software and/or application do the same. It is our policy to respond promptly to claims of intellectual property misuse. <br/><br/>All materials published under the Circle of 6® and/or Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> trademarks are protected by copyright, and owned or controlled by Tech 4 Good, or the party listed as the provider of the content, software or other materials. Commercial use of the materials is prohibited without the written permission of Tech 4 Good.  CIRCLE OF 6® and CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> are trademarks of Tech 4 Good.  Unauthorized use of the Circle of 6® and Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> trademarks are prohibited and may constitute trademark infringement.  Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> may seek and prosecute any infringements to the fullest extent of the law together with civil and criminal penalties.<br/><br/>No permission is granted here to User to use, or permit others to use, Tech 4 Good&apos;s icons, site address, trademarks and service marks, or other means to hyperlink other Internet App with any page in the Circle of 6® and/or Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup>&apos;s Web site, software and/or App.<br/><br/><b>Digital Millennium Copyright Act</b><br/><br/>Tech 4 Good respects intellectual property rights, and will deny access to our site to anyone who, in our discretion, repeatedly infringes the intellectual property rights of others. In addition, we will use reasonable efforts, in light of our resources, to accommodate generally accepted technical measures used by copyright owners to identify and protect their copyrighted works. If User believe materials posted on our site infringe rights User enjoy under copyright law in specific materials (collectively a &ldquo;Work&rdquo;), we request that User direct your concerns to our &ldquo;Designated Agent&rdquo; provided below, pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (17 U.S.C. §512) (hereafter the &ldquo;DMCA&rdquo;). Your notice to our Designated Agent should follow the notice provisions set out in the DMCA. Upon receiving your notice, we agree to respond to it and, if appropriate, remove or disable access to material User believes infringes your Work.<br/><br/>If User is a US copyright owner or an agent of a US copyright owner and believe that any user content or other content on the any Tech 4 Good website, such as the Circle of 6® Site and/or Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> infringes upon your copyrights, User may submit a notification pursuant to Title 17, United States Code, Section 512, the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (\"DMCA\") to our designated agent: Colvin IP PC, 375 Park Avenue, Suite 2607, New York, New York, 10152.  User acknowledges and agrees that upon receipt and notice of a claim of infringement, we may immediately remove the identified materials from the App without liability.<br/><br/>If User should have questions or comments about our these Terms and Conditions or about our privacy policy, or if User would like to obtain additional information regarding your privacy rights, please contact Colvin IP PC, 375 Park Avenue, Suite 2607, New York, New York, 10152.<br/><br/>All comments, feedback, postcards, suggestions, ideas, and other submissions disclosed, submitted, or offered to Tech 4 Good through our site or otherwise disclosed, submitted, or offered in connection with your use of our site (collectively &ldquo;User Comments&rdquo;) shall be and remain the property of Tech 4 Good. User agrees that Tech 4 Good shall be free to use, without restriction and without compensation to User, any ideas, concepts, know-how, suggestions, or techniques contained in any User Comments User send to us for any purpose whatsoever. Tech 4 Good has no obligation to respond to any User Comments, and we reserve the right, but undertake no duty, to review, edit, move, or delete any User Comments posted by users on our site, in our sole discretion and without notice.<br/><br/>All notices, request, demands and other communications required by this agreement shall be in writing to Colvin IP PC, 375 Park Avenue, Suite 2607, New York, New York, 10152, and except as expressly provided elsewhere in this agreement, shall be deemed to have been given at that time of delivery if personally delivered, or at the time of mailing, if mailed by first class, postage prepaid, and addressed to the party at its address as stated in this agreement.<br/><br/><b>Indemnification</b><br/><br/>User Agrees to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless, Tech 4 Good LLC its parents, subsidiaries, and affiliates, and each of their respective officers, directors, attorneys and employees from any and all claims, liabilities, costs, and expenses, including, but not limited to, attorneys&apos; fees and expenses, arising out a breach by User or any user of your account of these Terms and Conditions or privacy policy or arising out of a breach of your obligations, representation and warranties under these Terms and Conditions.   User Agrees to indemnify, defend, protect and hold harmless all of the Tech 4 Good and/or Circle of 6® Parties from and against all losses, claims, and expenses (including attorneys&apos; fees and costs) arising out of or relating to: (1) your breach of any terms of this Agreement, (2) the determination by a jurisdiction that User has improperly utilized the Services of Tech 4 Good to violate the laws and regulations of the jurisdiction; (3) your use of the App or your failure to pay any sums due Circle of 6® or any local government; or (4) your supplying inaccurate, out of date, errors or omissions, or otherwise incorrect information as well as any action taken by User as a direct or indirect use of the App and/or which result from the information displayed on the Circle of 6® and/or Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> web site.<br/><br/>Each user shall indemnify, defend and hold harmless Tech 4 Good, and its parent corporation and affiliates and their respective officers, employees and agents, and each of Tech 4 Good&apos;s software, App and/or application partners, from any and all claims, demands, damages, costs, and liabilities including reasonable attorneys&apos; fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of that user&apos;s acts or omissions, including claims arising out of that user&apos;s use of the App; his or her submission, posting or transmission of Content or his or her violation of the Terms.<br/><br/>User Agrees to indemnify and defend Tech 4 Good and its Affiliates from and against any and all claims, liabilities, damages, losses, costs, expenses, fees of any kind (including reasonable attorneys&apos; fees and legal costs), arising from or relating to: (a) any information (including Submissions) that User or anyone using your account submit, post, or transmit through the App or Tech 4 Good software and/or applications; (b) the use of the App or Tech 4 Good software and/or applications by User or anyone using your account; (c) the violation of these Terms of Use by User or anyone using your account; or (d) the violation of any rights of any third party, including intellectual property, privacy, publicity, or other proprietary rights by User or anyone using your account. Tech 4 Good reserves the right, at its own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by User. If we do assume the defense of such a matter, User will reasonably cooperate with Tech 4 Good in such defense.<br/><br/>User Agrees to defend, indemnify and hold Tech 4 Good and/or Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> harmless from and against any and all claims, damages, costs, and expenses, including attorney&apos;s fees, arising from or in any way related to your failure to comply with these Terms and Conditions or your use of our site.<br/><br/>The Parties agree that Tech 4 Good is not an insurer and no insurance coverage is offered herein. User&apos;s payments to Tech 4 Good are for the installation, use and service of an App.  Tech 4 Good does not guarantee that no losses will occur to User or others when using of the App. Tech 4 Good is not assuming liability and therefore shall not be liable to User for any loss or injury sustained by User as a result of any cause whatsoever, regardless of whether or not such loss or injury was caused by or contributed to by Tech 4 Good&apos;s negligent (including gross negligence) performance to any degree or failure to perform any obligation or strict products liability. User releases Tech 4 Good from any claims for contribution, indemnity or subrogation.<br/><br/>If anyone other than User, including your insurance, asks Tech 4 Good or Representatives to pay for any loss, damage, cost or expense (including economic losses, property damage, personal injury, or death) arising out of or from, in connection with, related to, as a consequence of, or resulting from any reason, including (1) the active or passive, sole, joint or several negligence of any kind or degree of Tech 4 Good or any of the Representatives, (2) the improper operation of the App, (3) a breach of contract, or (4) any claims for subrogation, indemnification or contribution, User and Payer agree to defend, indemnify and hold Tech 4 Good or its Representatives harmless (without any condition that Tech 4 Good or Representatives first pay) from any and all such loss, damage, cost and expense, including attorneys&apos; fees, which may be asserted against or incurred by Tech 4 Good or any of the Representatives in connection with any and all such claims to the fullest extent permitted by applicable law.  Your duty to indemnify, including the cost and duty to defend and hold Tech 4 Good and its Representatives harmless shall include all of the Tech 4 Good&apos;s personnel-related costs, overhead, experts&apos; fees, actual attorneys fees, court costs and all related expenses, including all fees and costs incurred to enforce and establish rights under this indemnification provision.  User on its behalf and any insurance carrier waives any right of subrogation User&apos;s insurance carrier may otherwise have against Tech 4 Good LLC or Tech 4 Good LLC&apos;s subcontractors arising out of this Agreement or the relation of the Parties hereto.<br/><br/><b>Waiver</b><br/><br/>Our failure to insist upon or enforce any provision of these terms of service shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right of Tech 4 Good.  The failure of either party to insist upon or enforce strict performance by the other party of any provision of this Agreement or to exercise any right under this Agreement shall not be construed as a waiver of the right of such party to assert or rely upon such provision or right in any other instance.<br/><br/>Any waiver of any breach of this Agreement, by User or the Tech 4 Good, shall not be construed as a waiver of any subsequent breach. Your rights and Tech 4 Good&apos;s rights hereunder shall be cumulative, and any rights hereunder may be exercised concurrently or consecutively and shall include all remedies available even though not expressly referred to herein.<br/><br/>USER RELEASES, WAIVE, DISCHARGE AND PROMISE NOT TO SUE OR BRING ANY CLAIM OF ANY TYPE AGAINST TECH 4 GOOD FOR LOSS, DAMAGE OR INJURY RELATING IN ANY WAY TO ANY SOFTWARE, APP OR SERVICES PROVIDED BY TECH 4 GOOD.<br/><br/><b>Modification</b><br/><br/>We reserve the right to modify or terminate Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> for any reason at any time without notice to the User.  Tech 4 Good may amend and/or change this Agreement at any time without notice to User.  We may change, move, discontinue, or delete portions of our App, or add to our App at any time.  The parties to this agreement acknowledge that Tech 4 Good retains sole authority to determine the technical operation of the App.  Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to comply with such modifications and be bound by the Agreement as amended. In addition, by accepting or using the Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> App, services, software, web site, User Agrees to periodically review this Agreement and be bound by any amendments to the Agreement.  Tech 4 Good shall not be liable to any user or other third party for any such modification, suspension or discontinuance except as expressly provided herein.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good may make improvements and/or changes in the products or services described in any Tech 4 Good Web site, including the Terms and Conditions of your use of this site, without liability.<br/><br/>Please print a copy of these Terms OF USE for User records and PLEASE check the Site frequently for any changes to these Terms of use.<br/><br/><b>Limitations On Liability</b><br/><br/>TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SERVICES AND CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> WEBAPP ARE PROVIDED ON AN \"AS IS\" AND &ldquo;AS AVAILABLE&rdquo; BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH RESPECT TO THE CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SERVICES AND CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> WEBAPP, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, AND ABSENCE OF ERRORS, BUGS, VIRUSES, AND/OR MECHANISMS WHICH MAY DISABLE, DAMAGE OR INTERFERE WITH COMPUTER SYSTEMS OR NETWORKS.<br/><br/>USER ACKNOWLEDGES THAT YOUR USE OF OUR SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK, THAT USER ASSUME FULL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ALL COSTS ASSOCIATED WITH ALL NECESSARY SERVICING OR REPAIRS OF ANY EQUIPMENT USER USE IN CONNECTION WITH<br/><br/>YOUR USE OF OUR SITE, AND THAT TECH 4 GOOD SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND RELATED TO YOUR USE OF THE APP.TECH 4 GOOD AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY, RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY, TIMELINESS, AND ACCURACY OF THE APP SERVICES WEBAPP FOR ANY PURPOSE OR THE AVAILABILITY OF ANY NETWORKS OR COMMUNICATIONS LINES OR FUNCTIONING OF ANY MOBILE PHONE OR DEVICE NECESSARY FOR THE APP SERVICES.<br/><br/>User Agrees that your use of the App and information on any Tech 4 Good web site is at User&apos;s own and sole risk. All Services are provided on an \"AS IS\" and \"AS AVAILABLE\" basis. Tech 4 Good disclaims all warranties and duties of any kind, express, implied or statutory, including, but not limited to, any implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a specific purpose, non-infringement or title, duties of workman-like effort, or lack of negligence. Tech 4 Good assumes no responsibility for errors or omissions on its web site and is not responsible in any way for the functionality, specifications, or any other aspect thereof. Tech 4 Good does not guarantee continuous, uninterrupted or secure access to Tech 4 Good or that defects in its web site will be corrected. Tech 4 Good reserves the right at any time and without prior notice to change the hours of operation to limit your access to the App in order to perform repairs, make modifications as a result of circumstances beyond the reasonable control of Tech 4 Good and to add or withdraw products or features to or from the App at any time. User is responsible for implementing sufficient procedures to satisfy your particular requirements for protection of your system and/or accuracy of data, and for maintaining a means of reconstruction of lost data. Without limiting the above, User Agrees that neither Tech 4 Good nor any of its parent corporations, subsidiaries, partners, employees, independent contractors, officers, directors, attorneys, agents, affiliates, representatives, successors and/or assigns (each a \"Tech 4 Good Party\"; collectively the Tech 4 Good Parties) makes any warranties or undertakes any duties regarding, without limitation, the following: (1) infringement of title or quiet enjoyment; (2) functionality, including functionality of search or retrieval software; (3) content, format, accuracy, completeness, or completion of forms; (4) receipt (timely or otherwise), approval and/or processing of documents by courts and/or any other government agencies; (5) appropriateness or propriety of documents handled with respect to any Services; (6) timeliness of Services; (7) uninterrupted, secure, error or virus-free Services or storage; (8) adequacy of fees paid to courts and/or other government agencies; (9) any alteration or destruction of a document resulting from third parties&apos; unauthorized access to or use of the App and/or application and any losses or damages or alteration of a document or information on any party&apos;s computer system or elsewhere resulting from the transmission of computer \"viruses\" or other damaging or destructive software or software components by or through Tech 4 Good.<br/><br/>The information on any Tech 4 Good Site and App is given &ldquo;as is&rdquo; and without warranties of any kind, either expressed or implied, including all warranties of usability and fitness for a particular purpose. There is no warranty that the Site or App will be available, uninterrupted, error-free, or free of viruses or other harmful components. Tech 4 Good is not liable to any person for any damages of any kind, including without limitation direct or indirect, incidental, or consequential damages, losses or expenses arising out of or in connection with the Site or App or use thereof, or in connection with any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, defect, delay in operation or transmission, network error, device theft, hotline error, computer virus or system failure, even if advised of possibility of such damages, losses or expenses.<br/><br/>In no event will Tech 4 Good be liable to any party for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, exemplary, consequential, or other damages (including, but not limited to, lost profits, business interruption, loss of programs or data) without regard to the form of action and whether in contract, tort, negligence, strict liability, or otherwise, arising out of or in connection with this site, any content on or accessed through this site or any site service linked to, or any copying, displaying, or use thereof.<br/><br/>This disclaimer of liability applies to any damages or injuries caused by the App, including, without limitation, those damages or injuries occurring as a result of: (i) any error, omission, deletion, or defect in the content available on the App; or (ii) any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, communication line failure, theft or destruction of records, information or data, unauthorised access to, alteration of, or use of records, information or data, whether for breach of contract, tort, negligence, defamation, or any other cause of action. Tech 4 Good does not warrant or guarantee that access to the App will be uninterrupted or error-free.<br/><br/>Applicable law may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to User.<br/><br/>Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup>, its officers, employees, representatives, agents, attorneys, or directors in no occasion will be held liable for and indirect, consequential, incidental, or punitive damages in the event not limited to loss in profits or loss of data.  Whatever the reason resulting in any claim may be, such as but not limited to personal injury, negligence, breach of contract, whether or not we were advised of the possibility of such damages at any time.<br/><br/>Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> takes no responsibility of action or lack thereof on the part of User&apos;s contacts, nor foreseen or unforeseen consequences resulting from initiated contacts. Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> takes no responsibility for the proper functioning of any networks or servers, or any communications that occur over such networks and servers. User Agrees that Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> shall have no liability to User or to any third party arising as a result of any networks or servers failing to perform in the manner intended, failure of Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> services to properly operate with your network or servers or from any errors occurring on your networks or servers as a result of your use of Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup>. User Agrees to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> and its affiliates, officers, directors, employees and agents from and against any and all third party claims (and any and all resulting losses, damages, liabilities, costs and expenses) alleging that your use of Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> violates, infringes or misappropriates the rights of any third party or violates applicable law.<br/><br/>To the fullest extent allowed by applicable law, User Agrees that none of the Tech 4 Good Parties will be liable to User, your successors, agents, heirs or assigns, and/or any other person or entity for general, special, incidental, consequential, indirect, exemplary or punitive damages of any kind, including, but not limited to, those damages resulting from loss of use, data, sales, goodwill, or profits, failure to meet any duty (including good faith or reasonable care) whether or not Tech 4 Good has been advised of the possibility, or under any legal or equitable theory of liability, including theories of tort, contract, or otherwise arising out of the use of the Tech 4 Good web site or Services or the termination of your use of the Tech 4 Good web site and Services.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good shall not have any liability to User and/or any third party as a result of the provision of any incorrect Personal Information provided to the App.<br/><br/>User understands that the Personal Information User provide to Us can be critical in the event of an emergency and the need to Use our Service. User also understand We can only rely on User to ensure that Your Personal Information is accurate, up-to-date complete and truthful. In providing Your Active Acceptance (and any time thereafter when User contact Us to update Your Personal Information or place a new Order), User Agrees that the Personal Information User provide Us will at all times be a truthful and accurate record of the Personal Information User wish to be disclosed to a clinical or emergency professional in the event of an emergency and User acknowledge that We and any clinical or emergency professional to which the Personal Information is disclosed are entitled to rely on such Personal Information.<br/><br/>User is responsible for ensuring that the Personal Information held by Us about User is complete, accurate and up to date and User will advise Us promptly of any changes to Your Personal Information. User acknowledge that it is Your responsibility to keep Your Personal Information up to date and that Your failure to do so can result in Us not being able to provide accurate information on User when the Emergency Service is called.<br/><br/>The User will be the only person who owns the phone, or whom is the primary user of the phone and who downloaded and activated the software.<br/><br/>The User will only use the App when all Information regarding its use and the User is accurate.<br/><br/>If the User does not possess the phone, this may delay the provision of emergency medical treatment to the User, since medical or clinical emergency professionals may not be able to identify the User&apos;s medical condition so readily. The User acknowledges this and assumes all risks in this regard.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good has no liability for any procedure and/or action that a responder, the police, or other third party or other nominated party carry out when the App is activated by User to call a contact and/or a government responder, such as the police, fire or ambulance.<br/><br/>Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> does not accept any responsibility or liability for your safety, including but not limited to: negligence or failure to act in a safe manner or follow emergency advice or protocol, personal injury, death or other consequences suffered by User or any third parties. Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> services is provided on an &ldquo;as is&rdquo; basis and is not liable for any loss, damage, errors or omissions in connection with your use of Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> services.  User understands and agrees that Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> is not liable for your safety.  User is solely responsible for taking appropriate safety precautions.<br/><br/>If medical emergency notification services are provided, I agree that the very nature of such services, regardless of any delay, involves uncertainty, risk and possible serious injury, disability or death, for which I will not attempt to hold Tech 4 Good responsible or liable whatsoever.  The Parties agree that the App is not designed or guaranteed to prevent any loss or injury.<br/><br/>If the User activates a communication for any reason, User shall (i) pay, without reimbursement from Tech 4 Good, any and all associated costs and expenses however incurred. If User fails to provide access to a responder to a communication, responder(s) may use forcible means to enter the Premises, which may result in damage to the Premises, all of which damage, cost and expense shall be borne solely by User without recourse to Tech 4 Good or Representatives. Tech 4 Good has no control over response times for responders. User hereby release Tech 4 Good and the Representatives for and from all claims, losses and damages that may arise from any forced entry or any delayed response by Responders.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good neither represents nor warrants that any service will prevent any loss, damage or injury to person or property, will function at a desired time, or provide any personal protection in any circumstance.  User acknowledges that Tech 4 Good is not an insurer, and that User assumes all risk for loss or injury to User&apos;s property or person. Tech 4 Good has made no representation or warranties, and hereby disclaims any warranty of merchantability or fitness for any particular use.<br/><br/>USER ACKNOWLEDGES THAT TO THE EXTENT THAT THE APP SERVICES ARE NOT A GUARANTEE OF SAFETY AGAINST PERSONAL HARM OR PREVENTION OF LOSS, LIABILITY, INJURY AND DAMAGE OF WHATSOEVER NATURE AND HOWSOEVER ARISING.<br/><br/>CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SHALL FURTHER NOT BE LIABLE TO USER FOR ANY DAMAGE, LOSS, LIABILITY OR INJURY OF WHATSOEVER NATURE AND HOWSOEVER ARISING THAT MAY RESULT FROM ANY FORCE MAJEURE OR CASUS FORTUITOUS INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO UNFORESEEABLE INTERRUPTIONS IN TELEPHONE, COMMUNICATIONS, INTERNET OR RADIO LINKS<br/><br/>USER AGREES TO ALWAYS USE COMMON SENSE AND SEEK HELP WHEN IT IS NEEDED. CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> CANNOT AND DOES NOT GUARANTEE THAT ANY EMERGENCY PERSONNEL WILL RESPOND IN A TIMELY MANNER OR AT ALL, OR THAT THE MOST APPROPRIATE PERSONNEL WILL RESPOND. ADDITIONALLY, EMERGENCY RESPONSE PERSONNEL MAY NOT RESPOND BECAUSE OF LOCAL LAWS, REGULATIONS OR POLICIES. USER SHOULD VERIFY THAT APPROPRIATE EMERGENCY PERSONNEL HAVE BEEN CONTACTED AND HAVE ALL INFORMATION NEEDED TO RESPOND TO THE EMERGENCY.<br/><br/>NO GUARANTEE; NO LIABILITY. TECH 4 GOOD&apos;S APP, SOFTWARE EQUIPMENT AND SERVICES DO NOT CAUSE AND CANNOT ELIMINATE OCCURRENCES OF ANY HARMFUL EVENTS, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PERSONAL INJURY, ASSAULT, CRIME, INJURY, FIRES, FLOODS, BURGLARIES, ROBBERIES AND MEDICAL PROBLEMS. OTHER THAN THE LIMITED WARRANTY AND/OR QUALITY SERVICE PLAN SET FORTH IN THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS.<br/><br/>TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, TECH 4 GOOD DISCLAIMS LIABILITY ON BEHALF OF ITSELF AND ITS AGENTS AND CONTRACTORS (WHICH AGENTS AND CONTRACTORS ARE THIRD PARTY BENEFICIARIES UNDER THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS) FOR ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY CAUSED BY ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, COMMUNICATION LINE FAILURE, THEFT OR DESTRUCTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO, ALTERATION OF, OR USE OF RECORD, WHETHER AS A RESULT OF BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORTUOUS BEHAVIOR, NEGLIGENCE, OR UNDER ANY OTHER CAUSE OF ACTION.<br/><br/>User waives the right to trial by jury in any suit, action or other legal proceeding in connection with this Agreement. This jury trial waiver cannot be revoked.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good takes no responsibility for the proper functioning of any networks or servers, or any communications that occur over such networks and servers. Tech 4 Good makes no representations or warranties as to the interoperability of the App with any network or servers. User acknowledge that Tech 4 Good shall have no liability to User or to any third party arising as a result of any networks or servers failing to perform in the manner intended, failure of the App to properly operate with your network or servers or from any errors occurring on your networks or servers as a result of your use of the App.<br/><br/>User acknowledge and recognize that the App is a social networking service provided through applications, mobile networks, and the internet, and that Tech 4 Good does not always control or endorse the involvement of its users in the App, including who is a user, administrator or co-administrator and, therefore, Tech 4 Good specifically disclaims any liability with regard to the Communication Services and any actions resulting from your participation in any Communication Service.  App users are not authorized Tech 4 Good spokespersons, and their views do not necessarily reflect those of Tech 4 Good.<br/><br/>Materials uploaded to a Communication Service may be subject to posted limitations on usage, reproduction and/or dissemination. User is responsible for adhering to such limitations if User downloads the materials.<br/><br/>NO SUIT OR ACTION SHALL BE BROUGHT AGAINST TECH 4 GOOD MORE THAN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE DATE OF THE INCIDENT THAT RESULTED IN THE LOSS, INJURY OR DAMAGE, OR THE SHORTEST DURATION PERMITTED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW IF GREATER THAN ONE (1) YEAR.<br/><br/>BENEFIT TO OTHERS. THE PROVISIONS OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SHALL APPLY TO AND BENEFIT TECH 4 GOOD AND ITS AGENTS, EMPLOYEES, CONTRACTORS, SUBSIDIARIES, DEALERS, AFFILIATES, PARENTS (BOTH DIRECT AND INDIRECT), AFFINITY MARKETERS AND OTHER PARTNERS.<br/><br/>In addition to the limitations on our liability set out herein, Tech 4 Good shall not be liable for any damage caused to or interference with any equipment or other Apps or content of any description by the use of the App.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good is neither responsible nor liable for any viruses or other contamination of your system nor for any delays, inaccuracies, errors or omissions arising out of your use of the Site or with respect to the material contained on the Site, including without limitation, any material posted on the Site.<br/><br/>USER ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, APPLICATIONS, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES INCLUDED IN OR AVAILABLE THROUGH THE CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SERVICES AND CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> WEBAPP MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS AND THAT CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SHALL HAVE NO LIABILITY FOR SUCH ERRORS. INFORMATION USER MAY RECEIVE VIA THE CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SERVICES OR CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> WEBAPP MAY NOT BE RELIED UPON BY USER FOR PERSONAL, SECURITY, MEDICAL, LEGAL OR FINANCIAL DECISIONS AND USER SHOULD CONSULT AN APPROPRIATE PROFESSIONAL FOR SPECIFIC ADVICE TAILORED TO YOUR SITUATION.<br/><br/>USER UNDERSTANDS AND AGREES THAT ANY MATERIAL OR INFORMATION DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SERVICES OR CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> WEBAPP IS DONE AT YOUR OWN RISK AND THAT USER WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE ARISING FROM DOING SO. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY USER FROM CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> OR THROUGH THE CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SERVICES OR CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> WEBAPP WILL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY MADE IN THESE TERMS OF USE.<br/><br/>USER ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OF ACTION, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE) OR OTHERWISE, IN NO EVENT WILL CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> OR ITS AFFILIATES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, SUCCESSORS AND ASSIGNS, BE LIABLE TO USER OR ANY OTHER PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT LOSS, DAMAGE, COST, EXPENSE OR LIABILITY OF ANY KIND (\"LOSS\") ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE AVAILABILITY, USE, RELIANCE ON, OR INABILITY TO USE THE CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SITE, INCLUDING (WITHOUT LIMITATION): (i) DAMAGES FOR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF BUSINESS AND OTHER PROFITS, LOSS OF PROGRAMS, COST OF REPLACING EQUIPMENT OR SOFTWARE OR LOSS OF RECORDS, INFORMATION OR DATA, LOSS OF USE OF DATA, LOSS OF REVENUE, LOSS OF GOODWILL, LOSS OF CUSTOMERS, LOSS OF OR DAMAGE TO REPUTATION, LOSS OF CAPITAL, DOWNTIME COSTS, LOSS UNDER OR IN RELATION TO ANY OTHER CONTRACT, OR LOSS OF ANTICIPATED SAVINGS OR BENEFITS; (ii) ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL LOSS; OR (iii) ANY LOSS ATTRIBUTABLE TO ERRORS, OMISSIONS, OR OTHER INACCURACIES IN THE CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SITE. THE EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY IN THIS SECTION 17 APPLIES EVEN IF CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SHALL HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS.<br/><br/>BECAUSE SOME STATES OR JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR PARTICULAR KINDS OF LOSS, IN SUCH STATES OR JURISDICTIONS, CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup>&apos;S LIABILITY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW (THEREBY MINIMIZING CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup>&apos;S LIABILITY TO USER TO THE LOWEST AMOUNT THAT APPLICABLE LAW PERMITS).<br/><br/>UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL I ATTEMPT TO HOLD TECH 4 GOOD LIABLE FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR PERSONAL INJURY OR DAMAGES TO PROPERTY. IF, NOTWITHSTANDING THE PROVISIONS OF THIS PARAGRAPH TECH 4 GOOD IS FOUND LIABLE FOR LOSS, DAMAGE OR INJURY UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY RELATING IN ANY WAY TO THE SOFTWARE, APP OR SERVICES PROVIDED BY TECH 4 GOOD.<br/><br/><b>Liquidated Damages</b><br/><br/>TECH 4 GOOD&apos;S LIABILITY TO ME SHALL BE LIMITED TO ANY PAYMENTS MADE BY USER TO TECH 4 GOOD OR $500, WHICHEVER IS GREATER. THIS AGREED-UPON AMOUNT IS NOT A PENALTY. RATHER, IT IS USER&apos;S SOLE REMEDY ALTERNATIVELY TO TERMINATION OF SERVICE ALONE. THE PROVISIONS OF THIS PARAGRAPH APPLY NO MATTER HOW THE LOSS, DAMAGE, INJURY OR OTHER CONSEQUENCE OCCURS,<br/><br/>EVEN IF DUE TO THE PERFORMANCE OR NONPERFORMANCE BY TECH 4 GOOD OF ITS OBLIGATIONS UNDER THIS CONTRACT OR FROM NEGLIGENCE (ACTIVE OR OTHERWISE), STRICT LIABILITY, VIOLATION OF ANY APPLICABLE CONSUMER PROTECTION LAW OR ANY OTHER THEORY OF LIABILITY OR ALLEGED FAULT ON THE PART OF TECH 4 GOOD, ITS AGENTS OR ITS EMPLOYEES.<br/><br/>IF USER IS DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF THE CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SERVICES OR CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> WEBAPP, OR WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OF USE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY, UNLESS LIQUIDATED DAMAGES ABOVE ARE LAWFULLY AWARDED, IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE APP AND ANY CIRCLE OF 6<sup>TM</sup> SERVICES.<br/><br/><b>Force Majeure</b><br/><br/>User understands that the technical processing, functioning and transmission of the App may involve (i) transmissions over various networks; and (ii) changes to content to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices. Tech 4 Good assumes no responsibility for the deletion or failure to store postings of content or other information submitted by User or other users to the App.  Tech 4 Good accepts no responsibility or liability for any interruption or delay of any service.  No liability for Phone Lines or Other Connectivity. Due to the potential for service interruption or outages on phone lines, internet service or mobile phone systems or other communication systems, none of which are within the control of the Tech 4 Good, your connection to the App and/or Tech 4 Good&apos;s service is not guaranteed. Users who use cable or Voice over Internet Protocol (VOIP) for their service are subject to additional consistency and reliability issues.  Tech 4 Good is not responsible for, and shall have no liability with respect to, service interruption, outages or failure of customer&apos;s telephone service.<br/><br/>To the extent Tech 4 Good may not, as a matter of applicable law, disclaim any implied warranty or limit its liabilities, the scope and duration of such warranty and the extent of Tech 4 Good&apos;s liability will be the minimum permitted under such law.  Some jurisdictions may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so some of the above exclusions may not apply to User. Check your local laws for any restrictions or limitations regarding the exclusion of implied warranties.<br/><br/>We shall not have any liability to User as a result of Our delay or failure to perform Our obligations under this Contract as a result of reasons beyond Our reasonable control including but not being limited to acts of God, war, riot, flood, earthquake, actual or threatened terrorism, power failures, equipment failure, communications interruptions, fire, labor disputes, subcontractor or supplier delays or failures, strikes, utility failures, civil commotion, malicious damage, explosion, governmental actions and any other similar events.<br/><br/>Nothing in this Contract shall exclude or limit any statutory rights which User has as a consumer; or our liability for death or personal injury due to our negligence.<br/><br/><b>Choice Of Law</b><br/><br/>User agrees these Terms and Conditions are governed by the laws of the United States of America and the laws of the State of New York.  User Agrees that exclusive jurisdiction for any claim or dispute with Tech 4 Good or relating in any way to your use of the App and/or any Tech 4 Good Site resides in the courts of the County of New York, State of New York, and User further agree and expressly consent to the exercise of personal jurisdiction in the courts of the County of New York, State of New York, in connection with any such dispute and including any claim involving Tech 4 Good or its affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, contractors, officers, directors, telecommunication providers and content providers.  Use of the App is unauthorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of these Terms of Use, including without limitation this section.<br/><br/><b>Termination</b><br/><br/>Tech 4 Good reserves the right to terminate this agreement with User at any time for any reason without notice. The User may terminate this agreement at any time without notice to Tech 4 Good by discontinuing use of the Site or the App.  Tech 4 Good reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate your access to the App and Tech 4 Good software and/or applications and the related services or any portion thereof at any time, without notice.  Tech 4 Good&apos;s obligation to provide Services shall terminate automatically as of the date any App and/or software is disabled and/or uninstalled by User and/or on a User device or equipment.<br/><br/>This Agreement is for an indefinite period of time and may be terminated by either party for any reason or no reason at all.  Tech 4 Good reserves the right to suspend access to the App, software and/or application, and Services at any time for any reason.<br/><br/>If User no longer accepts these Terms and Conditions, or any future modification to these Terms and Conditions, User must cease using the App.  Continued use of the App indicates User&apos;s continued acceptance of these Terms and Conditions.<br/><br/>If, for any reason, we believe that User has not complied with these Terms and Conditions, we may, at our sole discretion, cancel your access and/or use of the App immediately and without prior notice.  Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> may at any time terminate your account.  Circle of 6<sup>TM</sup> may at any time discontinue, suspend, or change any aspect of the site, software and/or services without informing User beforehand.<br/><br/>We shall have no liability to User and/or any third party resulting from Tech 4 Good&apos;s termination of service and/or removal of Personal Information.  User acknowledges that in the event of termination of this Contract, We have no duty to User, as to the provision of any service or the maintenance of your Personal Information.<br/><br/>Tech 4 Good&apos;s termination of any user&apos;s access to any or all Tech 4 Good site(s), the App, Tech 4 Good&apos;s software and/or application may be effected without notice and, on such termination, Tech 4 Good may immediately deactivate or delete user&apos;s account and/or bar any further access to such files. Tech 4 Good shall not be liable to any user or other third party for any termination of that user&apos;s access or account hereunder. In addition, a user&apos;s request for termination will result in deactivation but not necessarily deletion of the account. Tech 4 Good reserves the right to delete, or not delete, a user&apos;s account at Tech 4 Good&apos;s sole discretion, as well as to delete, or not delete, content at Tech 4 Good&apos;s sole discretion.<br/><br/>TECH 4 GOOD&apos;S RESPONSIBILITY AND OBLIGATIONS TO USER CEASE IMMEDIATELY WHEN THIS AGREEMENT IS TERMINATED OR THE SERVICES ARE SUSPENDED AN/OR CANCELED THE PROVISIONS OF THIS CLAUSE DO NOT IN ANY WAY DEROGATE FROM THE EXEMPTIONS FROM LIABILITY CONTAINED ELSEWHERE IN THIS AGREEMENT.<br/><br/><b>Severability</b><br/><br/>If any provision of this Contract is unenforceable, it shall not affect the enforceability of the remaining provisions of this Contract.<br/><br/>If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of these Terms and Conditions, or any portion thereof, to be unenforceable, that provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to affect the intent of these Terms &amp; Conditions, and the remainder of these Terms and Conditions shall continue in full force and effect.<br/><br/>User Agrees that this consent is severable from this Agreement and shall apply even in the event of termination of the Agreement.<br/><br/>Following termination, of these Terms and Conditions, limitations on Tech 4 Good&apos;s liability and indemnification by User shall survive termination and continue to apply.<br/><br/><b>Headings</b>The headings and paragraph titles used herein are solely for convenience of the parties only and shall not be considered in construing the provisions of this Agreement. In this Agreement, the word &ldquo;including&rdquo; is not a word of limitation but means &ldquo;including, without limitation or example.&rdquo;<br/><br/><b>Access And Use</b>User understands accepts these Terms and Conditions herein without limitation or qualification.  User expressly agrees to and accepts these Terms and Conditions herein.  Additionally by any use of the App User continues to agree and continues to be bound by these Terms and Conditions.<br/><br/>AS A CONDITION TO AND IN CONSIDERATION OF ACCESSING AND USING THE APP, USER AGREES TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE AND BY OUR PRIVACY POLICY.  IF USER DOES NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, USER SHOULD NOT USE THE APP AND/OR SHOULD NOT USE/VISIT ANY TECH 4 GOOD SITE.<br/><br/>YOUR USE OF ANY OF THE SITE(S), SOFTWARE AND/OR APPLICATION CONSTITUTES AGREEMENT WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE SET FORTH HEREIN (THE \"TERMS\").<br/><br/>ADDITIONALLY, USER INDICATES ACCEPTANCE BY CLICKING ON THE APPROPRIATE BUTTON BELOW, OR BY DOWNLOADING, INSTALLING, ACTIVATING THE APP AND/OR USING ANY TECH 4 GOOD APP, SOFTWARE AND/OR SERVICES, USER AGREESS TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE.<br/><br/><b>Acceptance</b><br/><br/>User certifies that User has read and understands this Agreement and states that User Agrees to be bound by the Terms and Conditions contained in this Agreement. User Agrees to comply with all city, county, state and federal laws and ordinances relating to use of the App.<br/><br/><b>Copyright Notice</b><br/><br/>Copyright 2014 by Tech 4 Good LLC, ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
            ]]>
    </string>
</resources>